A Guide to the R. Bruce Merrifield papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA415
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject Files, 3
  - Unfoldered Materials (Box 115, Folder 795-799)
    Includes: "Automated Solid-Phase Organic Synthesis in Micro-Plate Wells. Synthesis of N-(Alkoxy-Acyl)Amino Alcohols" by Krchnk, Weichsel, Lebl, and Felder "Cocrystal Structure of the Messenger RNA 5' Cap-Binding Protein (elF4E) Bound to 7-methyl-GDP" by Marcotrigiano, Gingras, Sonenberg, and Burley "Solid-Phase Synthesis of Artificial -Sheets" by Holmes, Smith, and Nowick "A Novel Algorithm for the Coupling Control in Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis" by Bagno, Bicciato, Dettin, and Di Bello "Some 'Difficult Sequences' Made Easy: A Study of Interchain Association in Solid-Phase Peptide Synthesis" by Johnson, Owen, Quibell, and Sheppard "UBA1: An Essential Yeast Gene Encoding Ubiquitin-Activating Enzyme" by McGrath, Jentsch, and Varshavsky "Cis-trans Recognition and Subunit-Specific Degradation of Short-Lived Proteins" by Johnson, Gonda, and Varshavsky "The Recognition Component of the N-end Rule Pathway" by Bartel, Wnning, and Varshavsky "Cloning and Functional Analysis of the Arginyl-tRNA0protein Transferase Gene ATE1 of Saccharomyces cerevisiae" by Balzi, Choder, Chen, Varshavsky, and Goffeau "In Vivo Degradation of a Transcriptional Regulator: The Yeast 2 Repressor" by Hochstrasser and Varshavsky "Secondary Structure of Src Homology 2 Domain of c-abl by heteronuclear NMR Spectroscopy in Solution" by Overduin, Mayer, Rios, Baltimore, and Cowburn "Three Diminsional Solution Structure of the Src Homology 2 Domain of c-Alb" by Overduin, Rios, Mayer, Baltimore, and Cowburn "Synthesis of 13C- and 15N-labelled tert-Butoxycarbonyl (Boc) Glycines and Glycine Amides as Precursors and Simple Models of Backbone-labelled Peptides" by Grehn, Bondesson, Pehk, and Ragnarsson "Direct Synthesis of N-Protected Chiral Amino Acids from Imidodicarbonates Employing Either Mitsunobu or Triflate Alkylation. Feasibility Study Using Lactate with Particular Reference to 15N-Labelling" by Degerbeck, Fransson, Grehn, and Ragnarsson "Synthesis of 15N-Labelled Chiral Boc-Amino Acidds from Triflates: Enantiomers of Leucine and Phenylalanine" by Degerbeck, Fransson, Gregh, and Ragnarsson "Synthesis, Properties and Use of Nitridotricarbonic Acid Tri-tert-Butyl Ester" by Degerbeck, Grehn, and Ragnarsson "Disulfide Bond Formation using Silylchloride-Sulfoxide System for the Synthesis of Cystine-Peptide" by Akaji, Tatsumi, Yoshida, Kimura, Fujiwara, and Kiso "Synthesis and Biological Activities of Atrial Natriuretic Polypeptide Analogs" by Kiso, Shimokura, Hosoi, Fujisaki, Fujiwara, and Yoshida "Synthesis and Characterization of Bivalent Peptide Ligands Targeted to G-Protein-Coupled Receptors" by Carrithers and Lerner "Quantitative Analysis of Amino Acids on Merrifield Resin by Microwave Hydrolysis" by Yu, Chen, Chiou, and Wang "The Four-Component Condensation (4CC): A New Versatile Method for the Synthesis of Substituted Prolyl Peptides" by Nutt and Joulli [Reprint in Russian, " "] A Micromethod for Complete Removal of Dodecyl Sulfate from Proteins by Ion-Pair Extraction" by Henderson, Oroszlan, and Konigsberg "An Amphiphilic Structure of the Ninth Component of Human Complement: Evidence from Analysis of Fragments Produced by -Thrombin" by Biesecker, Gerard, and Hugli "Accelerated Chemical Synthesis of Peptides and Small Proteins" by Miranda and Alewood "Antimetabolites: A Review" by Shaw "Incorporation of Gluatime Repeats Makes Protein Oligomerize: Implications for Neurodegenerative Diseases" by Stott, Blackburn, Butler, and Perutz "Solvent and Reagent Accessibility within Oligo(ethyleneglycol) Cross-linked Polystyrene Beads" by Wilson, Paech, Zhou, and Kurth "Diversomer Libraries: An Approach to Non-Peptide, Non-Oligomeric Chemical Diversity" by Dewitt, Kiely, Stankovic, Schroeder, Cody, and Pavia "Purification and Characterization of a Novel Zinc-Proteinase from Cultures of Aeromonas hydrophila" by Loewy, Santer, Wieczorek, Blodgett, Jones, and Cheronis "Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis" by Sheppard "Total Chemical Synthesis of Human Activin A [12-116] and Related Large Loop Polypeptides" by Deah, Allen, Clay, Warner, and Hearn "Antibody Remodeling: A General Solution to the Design of a Metal-Coordination Site in an Antibody Binding Pocket" by Roberts, Iverson, Iverson, Benkovic, Lerner, Getzoff, and Tainer "Mutation of a Conserved Cysteine in the X-Linked Cone Opsins Causes Color Vision Deficiencies by Disrupting Protein Folding and Stability" by Kazmi, Sakmar, and Ostrer "Time-Resolved Spectroscopy of the Early Photolysis Intermediates of Rhodopsin Schiff Base Counterion Mutants" by Jger, Lewis, Zvyaga, Szundi, Sakmar, and Kliger "The Steric Trigger in Rhodopsin Activation" by Shieh, Han, Sakmar, and Smith "Chromophore Structural Changes in Rhodopsin from Nanoseconds to Microseconds Following Pigment Photolysis" by Jger, Lewis, Zvyaga, Szundi, and Sakmar "Partial Agonist Activity of 11-cis-Retinal in Rhodopsin Mutants" by Han, Lou, Nakanishi, Sakmar, and Smith "Properties of Early Photolysis Intermediates of Rhodopsin are Affected by Glycine 121 and Phenylalanine 261" by Jger, Han, Lewis, Szundi, Sakmar, and Kliger "The C9 Methyl Group of Retinal Interacts with Glycine-121 in Rhodopsin" by Han, Groesbeek, Sakmar, and Smith "AMD3100, A Small Molecule Inhibitor of HIV-1 Entry via the CXCR4 Co-Receptor" by Donzella, Schols, Lin, Est, Nagashima, Maddon, Allaway, Sakmar, Henson, De Clercq, and Moore "Rhodopsin: A Prototypical G Protein-Coupled Receptor" by Sakmar "Amino-Terminal Substitutions in the CCR5 Coreceptor Impair gp120 Binding and Human Immunodeficiency Virus Type 1 Entry" by Dragic, Trkola, Lin, Nagashima, Kajumo, Zhao, Olson, Wu, Mackay, Allaway, Sakmar, Moore, and Maddon "Role of the C9 Methyl Group in Rhodopsin Activation: Characterization of Mutant Opsins with the Artificial Chromophore 11-cis-9-Demethylretinal" by Han, Groesbeek, Smith, and Sakmar "Tinkering with Enzymes: What Are We Learning?" by Knowles "Cleavage and Deprotection of MBHA-Resin Peptides with Hydrogen Bromide" by Wang, Wang, Hughes, Leopold, Wu, Tam, and Merrifield "Macromolecular Assemblage in the Design of a Synthetic AIDS Vaccine" by Deefort, Nardelli, Huang, Ho, and Tam "Characterization of Sulfated Glucuronic Acid Containing Glycolipids Reacting with IgM M-Protins in Patients with Neuropathy" by Ariga, Kohriyama, Freddo, Latov, Saito, Kon, Ando, Suzuki, Hemling, Rinehart, Jr., Kusunoki, and Yu "Molecular Cloning, Sequencing, and Expression of an 2-Adrenergic Receptor Complementary DNA from Rat Brain" by Chalberg, Duda, Rhine, and Sharma "Protein Structure Determination in Solution by Nuclear Magnetic Resonance Spectroscopy" by Wthrich "Voltage Gating of Conductance in Lipid Bilayers Induced by Porin from Outer Membrane of Neisseria ghonorrhoeae" by Mauro, Blake, and Labarca "Automated Solid-Phase Peptide Synthesis" by Erickson, Lukas, and Prystowsky "Challenging the Three-Dimensional Structure of Ribosomes" by Yonath and Wittmann "The Allosteric Three-Site Model for the Ribosomal Elongation Cycle: Features and Future" by Nierhaus "Effect of Nucleotide Substitution on the Peptidyltransferase Activity of 2'(3')-O-(Aminoacyl) Oligonucleotides" by Tezuka and Chldek "Combined Solid Phase/Solution Synthesis of a 31-Residue Vasoactive Intestinal Peptide Analog" by Felix, Zhao, Lambros, Ahmad, Liu, Daniewski, Michalewsky, and Heimer "Novel Amine Chemistry Based on DMAP-Catalyzed Acylation" by Ragnarsson and Grehn "SPOCC: A Resin for Solid Phase Organic Chemistry and Enzymatic Reactions on Solid Phase" by Rademann, Grtli, Melsal, and Bock "Expressed Protein Ligation: A General Method for Protein Engineering" by Muir, Sondhi, and Cole "Solution Structures of FcRI -Chain Mimics: A -hairpin Peptide and Its Retroenantiomer" by McDonnell, Fushman, Cahill, Sutton, and Cowburn "Cyclic Peptides from Linear Unprotected Peptide Precursors through Thiazolidine Formation" by Botti, Pallin, and Tam "Potent, Long-Acting Bradykinin Antagonists for a Wide Range of Applications" by Stewart, Gera, Chan, Whalley, Hanson, and Zuzack "Synthesis and Expression of Synthetic Genes: Applications to Structure-Function Studies of Receptors" by Carruthers and Sakmar "Characterization of Rhodopsin Mutants that Bind Transducin but Fail to Induce GTP Nucleotide Uptake" by Ernst, Hofmann, and Sakmar "Photoactivated State of Rhodopsin and How It Can Form" by Fahmy, Siebert, and Sakmar "Characterization of Deletion and Truncation Mutants of the Rat Glucagon Receptor" by Unson, Cypess, Kim, Goldsmith, Carruthers, Merrifield, and Sakmar "Properties and Photoactivity of Rhodopsin Mutants" by Sakmar and Fahmy "Antibodies against Specific Extracellular Epitopes of the Glucagon Receptor Block Glucagon Binding" by Unson, Cypess, Wu, Goldsmith, Merrifield, and Sakmar "Characterization of the Mutant Visual Pigment Responsible for Congenital Night Blindness: A Biochemical and Fourier-Transform Infrared Spectroscopy Study" by Zvyaga, Fahmy, Siebert, and Sakmar "Specific Tryptophan UV-Absorbance Changes are Probes of the Transition of Rhodopsin to Its Active State" by Lin and Sakmar "The Effects of Amino Acid Replacements of Glycine 121 on Transmembrane Helix 3 of Rhodopsin" by Han, Lin, Smith, and Sakmar "Functional Interaction of Transmembrane Helices 3 and 6 in Rhodopsin" by Han, Lin, Minkova, Smith, and Sakmar "Spectroscopic Evidence for Altered Chromophore-Protein Interactions in Low-Temperature Photoproducts of the Visual Pigment Responsible for Congenital Night Blindness" by Fahmy, Zvyaga, Sakmar, and Siebert "Rhodopsin Activation Blocked by Metal-Ion-Binding Sites Linking Transmembrane Helices C and F" by Sheikh, Zvyaga, Lichtarge, Sakmar, and Bourne "The Chemist's Magic Bullets: Selectivity as a Guiding Principle in Biomedical Research" by Witkop "Reproductive Endocrine and Endometrial Effects of Raloxifene Hydrochloride, a Selective Estrogen Receptor Modulator, in Women with Regular Menstrual Cycles" by Baker, Draper, Paul, Allerheiligen, Grant, Shifren, and Jaffe "A Controlled Trial of Raloxifene (LY139481) HCl: Impact on Bone Turnover and Serum Lipid Profile in Healthy Postmenopausal Women" by Draper, Flowers, Huster, Neild, Harper, and Arnaud "Selective Estrogen Receptor Modulators and Postmenopausal Women's Health" by Hol, Cox, Bryant, and Draper "Effects of Raloxifene on Bone Mineral Density, Serum Cholesterol Concentrations, and Uterine Endometrium in Postmenopausal Women" by Delmas, Bjarnason, Mitlak, Ravoux, Shah, Huster, Draper, and Christiansen "Raloxifene and Estrogen: Comparative Bone-Remodeling Kinetics" by Heaney and Draper "Effects of Raloxifene Hydrochloride on the Endometrium of Postmenopausal Women" by Boss, Huster, Neild, Glant, Eisenhut, and Draper "Secondary Structures of Proteins and Peptides in Amphiphilic Environments (A Review)" by Kaiser and Kzdy "Inhibition of the N-end Rule Pathway in Living Cells" by Baker and Varshavsky
  - Unfoldered Materials (Box 116, Folder 800-804)
    Includes: A 1987 Laboratory Animal Science Addendum to the 1977 Rockefeller University Report: A Visit to the People's Republic of China" "Reevaluation of the HF Procedure for Synthesizing High Molecular Weight Peptides" by Chino, Kumagaye, Masui, Kimura, and Sakakibara "Modified Polystyrenes: Effects of Pendant Functional Groups on Thermal Stability" by Bhatti, Davies, Dollimore, and Sood "DRIFT Study of Functional Group Interconversions on Modified Polystyrenes" by Davies and Sood "Making Antibodies without the Antigens" "Derivation and Diversification of Monoclonal Antibodies (Nobel Lecture)" by Khler "The Generative Grammar of the Immune System (Nobel Lecture)" by Jerne "Comparison of Reversed-Phase and Cation-Exchange for High-Performance Liquid Chromatography for Separating Closely Related Peptides: Separation of ASP76-Human Parathyroid Hormone (1-84) from ASN76-Human Parathyroid Hormone (1-84)" by Kumagaye, Takai, Chino, Kimura, and Sakakibara "Molecular Level Fabrication Techniques and Molecular Electronic Devices" by Carter "The Molecular Device Computer: Point of Departure for Large Scale Cellular Automata" by Carter "Protein Thiolation and Reversible Protein-Protein Conjugation" by Carlsson, Drevin, and Axn "Renaturation of Soluble and Immobilized Ribonuclease: Are the Polypeptide Folding Pathways for Structure Formation the Same for Soluble Proteins and for Proteins Associated with a Surface?" by Janolino, Swaisgood, and Horton "The Kinetics of Ion Exchange Processes" by Soldano "Robotic Orchestration of Organic Reactions: Yield Optimization via an Automated System with Operator-Specified Reaction Sequences" by Frisbee, Nanta, Kramer, and Fuchs "Aromatic-Aromatic Interaction: A Mechanism of Protein Structure Stabilization" by Burley and Petsko "Vaccines for the Third World" by Leeper "Production and Use of Antibodies against Synthetic Peptides" by Walter "Prediction of the Secondary Structure of Proteins from their Amino Acid Sequence" by Chou and Fasman "General Method for the Rapid Solid-Phase Synthesis of Large Numbers of Peptides: Specificity of Antigen-Antibody Interaction at the Level of Individual Amino Acids" by Houghten "Synthesis of Galanin, a New Gastrointestinal Polypeptide" by Yajima, Futaki, Rujii, Akaji, Funakoshi, Sakurai, Katakura, Inoue, Hosotani, Tobe, Segawa, Inoue, Tatemoto, and Mutt "Application of S-1-Adamantylcysteine to the Synthesis of a 37-Residue Peptide Amide corresponding to Human Calcitonin Gene-related Peptide (hCGRP)" by Fujii, Yajima, Otaka, Funakoshi, Nomizu, Akaji, Yamamoto, Torizuka, Kitagawa, Akita, Ando, Kawamoto, Shimonishi, and Takao "Electrostatic Interactions in Sperm Whale Myoglobin" by Garcia-Moreno, Chen, March, Gurd, and Gurd "Aliphatic Semisynthetic Variants of the Amino-Terminal Residue of Sperm Whale Myoglobin: Enrichment with 13C and Determination and Interpretation of Terminak pK Values" by Busch, Maskalick, Neireiter, Harris, and Gurd "Application of Nin-Mesitylenesulfonyl-tryptophan for the Syntheses of Neuromedin B and Neuromedin C" by Fujii, Futaki, Akaji, Yajima, Inoue, and Segawa "Synthesis of a 42 Residue Peptide Corresponding to the Entire Amino Acid Sequence of Human GIP" by Yajima, Fujii, Akaji, Sakurai, Nomizu, Mizuta, Aono, Moriga, Inoue, Hosotani, and Tobe "Synthesis of a Tripentacontapeptide with Epidermal Growth Factor Activity" by Akaji, Fujii, Yajima, Hayashi, Mizuta, Aono, and Moriga "3-(3-p-Methoxybenzylthiopropionyl)-thiazolidine-2-thione and Its Analogs as Reagents for the Introduction of the Mercapto Group into Peptides and Proteins" by Fujii, Akaji, Hayashi, and Yajima "Synthesis of the Protected Tetracosapeptide Corresponding to Positions 30-53 of Mouse Epidermal Growth Factor (EGF)" by Akaji, Fujii, and Yajima "Application of New Heterobifunctional Crosslinking Reagents for the Preparation of Neurokinin (A and B)-BSA (Bovine Serum Albumin) Conjugates" by Fujii, Hayashi, Katakura, Akaji, Yajima, Inouye, and Segawa "40 Years of Peptide Chemistry at a Max-Planck-Institute" by Wnsch "Human Immunoglubulin G1 Hinge Region: Synthesis of Related Peptides and Their Conformational Features" by Moroder, Bovermann, and Wnsch "A New Reagent for the Preparation of Glycoconjugates" by Moroder "Stimulation of Guanylate Cyclase Activity by Irreversible Binding of Atrial Natriuretic Peptide to Its Receptor" by Iwasa, Furuyama, Hayashi, and Ohnuma "The Polyamide Method of Solid Phase Peptide and Oligonucleotide Synthesis" by Atherton, Gait, Sheppard, and Williams ""New Procedures in Solid Phase Synthesis. Use of Fluorenylmethoxycarbonyl Amino-Acids for peptide Synthesis on Polydimethylacrylamide Supports in Stepwise and Fragment Condensation Strategies" by Atheron, Sheppard, and Williams "Chemical Synthesis of Peptides and Proteins" by Kent "Structure/Function Analysis of Synthetic/Recombinant Derivatives of Transforming Growth Factor-Alpha" by Defeo-Jones, Tai, Wgrzyn, Vuocolo, Vaker, Payne, Garsky, Oliff, and Riemen "Solid-Phase Synthesis of Porcine Carkiodilatin 88 (pCDD 88)" by Nokihara and Semba "Regiospecific Synthesis of -Hydroxybutenolide. Photosensitized Oxygenation of Substituted 2-Trimethylsilylfuran" by Katsumura, Hori, Fujiwara, and Isoe "The DNA Repair Gene RAD6 Encodes a Ubiquitin-Conjugating Enzyme" by Jentsch, McGrath, and Varshavsky "The Yeast Polyubiquitin Gene is Essential for Resistance to High Temperatures, Starvation, and Other Stresses" by Finley, zkaynak, and Varshavsky "In Vivo Half-Life of a Protein is a Function of Its Amino-Terminal Residue" by Bachmair, Finley, and Varshavsky "The Yeast Ubiquitin Genes: A Family of Natural Gene Fusions" by zkaynak, Finley, Solomon, and Varshavsky "Electrophoretic Assay for DNA-Binding Proteins" by Varshavsky "Post-Separation Detection of Nucleic Acids and Proteins by Neutron Activation" by Snapka, Kwok, Bernard, Harling, and Varshavsky "Enhancement of Immunoblot Sensitivity by Heating of Hydrated Filters" by Swerdlow, Finley, and Varshavsky
  - Unfoldered Materials (Box 117, Folder 805)
    Includes: "A Mammalian High Mobility Group Protein Recognizes Any Stretch of the Six AT Base Pairs in Duplex DNA" by Solomon, Strauss, and Varshavsky "Synthetic Peptide Antagonists of Glucagon" by Unson, Andreu, Gurzenda, and Merrifield "Symmetrical Anhydride Rearrangement Leads to Three Different Dipeptide Products" by Benoiton and Chen "High-Performance Liquid Chromatography of Epimeric N-protected Peptide Acids and Esters for Assessing Racemization" by Benoiton, Lee, Liberek, Steinauer, and Chen "1H n.m.r. Long-Range Coupling in 2,4-Disubstituted-5(4H)-oxazolones and 4-Alkyl-5(2H)-oxazolones Generated Therefrom by the Action of Triethylamine" by Chen and Benoiton "Mixed Carboxylic-Carbonic Acid Anhydrides of Acylamino Acids and Peptides as a Convenient Source of 2,4-dialkyl-5(4H)-oxazolones" by Chen, Slebioda, and Benoiton "Racemization of Acylamino Acids and the Carboxy-terminal Residue of Peptides" by Chen and Benoiton "Racemization during Aminolysis of Mixed and Symmetrical Anhydrides of N-Alkoxycarbonylamino Acids by Amino Acid Anions in Aqueous Dimethylformamide" by Benoiton, Lee, and Chen "Isopropyl Chloroformate as a Superior Reagent for Mixed Anhydride Generation and Couplings in Peptide Synthesis" by Benoiton, Lee, and Chen "A New Segment Synthesis of -Inhibin-92 by the Acyl Disulfide Method" by Yamashiro and Li
  - University Business (Box 117, Folder 806)
  - University Business, Patents (Box 117, Folder 807)
  - University Fellows (Box 117, Folder 808)
  - Unlabeled Folder (Box 117, Folder 809-811, Box 118, Folder 812-817, Box 119, Folder 818)
    Includes: "Synthesis of Sulfated Peptides" by Musiol, Escherich and Moroder
  - Unsaturation and Aldehydes (Box 119, Folder 819)
  - Urethane Acylation, LAGV Model Peptide (Box 119, Folder 820)
  - Use of Methyl Benzenes as Solvents for Acidic Deprotection Reagents (Box 119, Folder 821)
  - Video, Felix, Barany, and Merrifield Symposium (Box 119, Folder 822)
  - Video, "Peptide and Protein Synthesis" (Box 119, Folder 823)
  - Video Text, Peptide and Protein Video (Box 119, Folder 824)
  - Video, Active Video Material (Box 119, Folder 825)
  - Video, Unlabeled Folder (Box 120, Folder 826-829, Box 121, Folder 830-833)
  - Video, Video Materials (Box 122, Folder 834)
  - Viking Project, 1970-1971 (Box 122, Folder 835-836)
  - VIP (Vasoactive Intestinal Peptide) (Box 122, Folder 837)
  - Vipont (Box 122, Folder 838, Box 123, Folder 839-841, Box 124, Folder 842-845, Box 125, Folder 846)
  - Vipont Laboratories (Box 125, Folder 847)
  - Waters Associates (Box 125, Folder 848)
  - Wei-Jun Reports (Box 125, Folder 849)
  - Weissman Leukocyte Interferon (Box 125, Folder 850)
  - Wong, Tai Wai, Thymosin (Box 125, Folder 851)
  - Xanthone Chemistry (Box 125, Folder 852)
- Laboratory Files, 4
  This series is further divided into Administration and Notes and Notebooks; both groups are arranged alphabetically.
  - Administration
    - Anagani, Bhavani (Box 126, Folder 853)
    - Anagani, Bhavani (Box 126, Folder 853A)
    - Andreu, David (Box 126, Folder 854)
    - Andreu, David (Box 126, Folder 854A)
    - Annual Report Material, 1973-1979 (Box 126, Folder 855)
    - Appointment Letters (Box 126, Folder 856-857)
    - Barany, George (Box 126, Folder 858)
    - Barany, George (Box 126, Folder 858A)
    - Budget, 1995-2003 (Box 126, Folder 859-860, Box 127, Folder 861-866)
    - Budget, David Lyons, FY1992, 1990 (Box 128, Folder 867)
    - Budget Expenditure Summaries, 1966-967 (Box 128, Folder 868)
    - Budget, James Tam, 1986-1990 (Box 128, Folder 869)
    - Budget Meetings, FY1995, 1994 (Box 128, Folder 870)
    - Budget Meetings, David Lyons, 1993 (Box 128, Folder 871)
    - Budget Recommendations, 1988-1992 (Box 128, Folder 872)
    - Budget Reports, 1998-2005 (Box 128, Folder 873-875, Box 129, Folder 876-877)
    - "Bulk TLC Order", 1976-1979 (Box 129, Folder 878)
    - Burke, Henry (Box 129, Folder 879-880)
    - Certificate of Fitness (Box 129, Folder 881)
    - Certification Reports (Box 129, Folder 882)
    - ChemTech Synthesizer (Box 129, Folder 883)
    - Controlled Substances (Box 129, Folder 884)
    - Copas Bead Sorter (Box 129, Folder 885)
    - Cowburn Grant (Box 130, Folder 886)
    - Curriculum Vitae (Box 130, Folder 887)
    - Curriculum Vitae and Bibliography of Bruce Wayne Erickson, 1977 (Box 130, Folder 888)
    - de Lencastre, Alexandre (Box 130, Folder 889)
    - de Lencastre, Alexandre (Box 130, Folder 889A)
    - Experiments for Memo and Jim (Box 130, Folder 890)
    - Glucagon Project Status (Box 130, Folder 891)
    - Glucagon Receptor; Sakmar (Box 130, Folder 892)
    - Glucagon Renewal, 1994-1998 (Box 130, Folder 893)
    - Grant AM01260, 1962-1967 (Box 130, Folder 894-895)
    - Grant AM03386, 1963-1964 (Box 131, Folder 896)
    - Grant AM3386 (Box 131, Folder 897)
    - Grant Application, "Solid Phase Synthesis of Peptides and Proteins", 1978 (Box 131, Folder 898)
    - Grant Application, "Solid Phase Synthesis of Peptides and Proteins", 1978 (Box 131, Folder 898A)
    - Grant Application, "Synthetic Analogs of Glucagon for Studies on Diabetes", 1978 (Box 131, Folder 899)
    - Grant Application, "Synthetic Analogs of Glucagon for Studies on Diabetes", 1978 (Box 131, Folder 899A)
    - Grant Applications, Erickson (Box 131, Folder 900)
    - Grant Applications, Erickson (Box 131, Folder 900A)
    - Grant DK01260, 1986-1994 (Box 132, Folder 901-904, Box 133, Folder 905-908)
      Includes: Grant DK01260, 13-20, 20-33, 34-41, 40
    - Grant DK24039, 1993-1998 (Box 133, Folder 909, Box 134, Folder 910-916, Box 135, Folder 917-920)
      Includes: Grant DK24039, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 20, Renewal
    - Grant Proposals, 1981-1983 (Box 135, Folder 921)
    - Grants (Box 135, Folder 922)
    - Grants - Old (Box 135, Folder 923)
    - Gregory, John D., Exams (Box 135, Folder 924)
    - Haser, Paul (Box 135, Folder 925)
    - Hazardous Chemicals Inventory (Box 136, Folder 926)
    - Heath, William F. (Box 136, Folder 927)
    - Heath, William F. (Box 136, Folder 927A)
    - HF (Hydrogen Fluoride) Apparatus (Box 136, Folder 928)
    - Hoffman La Roche Grant, 1967-1985 (Box 136, Folder 929)
    - Hou, Jian-Min (Box 136, Folder 930)
    - Hou, Jian-Min (Box 136, Folder 930A)
    - IBM Synthesizer, Whitney, 1985 (Box 136, Folder 931)
    - Instruction Manuals (Box 137, Folder 932-933)
    - Instrument Manuals (Box 137, Folder 934-935, Box 138, Folder 936-939)
    - Job Requests (Box 139, Folder 940)
    - Juvvadi, Padmaja (Box 139, Folder 941-943)
    - Juvvadi, Padmaja (Box 139, Folder 943A)
    - Kaiser, Emil (Centocor) (Box 139, Folder 944)
    - Kaiser, Emil (Centocor) (Box 139, Folder 944A)
    - Kubiak, Teresa (Box 139, Folder 945)
    - Kubiak, Teresa (Box 139, Folder 945A)
    - Lab Appointments (Box 139, Folder 946)